hotelthailand.com 2007-04-02

# Hotel Thailand Privacy Policy Information - Thailand Hotels-large selection of hotels and resorts in Thailand, find your accommodations online.

This is fully functional new beta version of our site. Change to this version from old site will be in stages.

| **You are in control of the information you provide to HotelThailand.com**  
---  
As a member of HotelThailand.com, you are in complete control of your travel planning needs. This includes controlling the use of information you provide to HotelThailand.com. The bottom line is that we respect and will continue to respect the privacy of our customers who use HotelThailand.com. 

Because protecting your privacy is important to us, you can be assured that HotelThailand.com discloses the following: 

  * How we gather your personal information 
  * What Information we gather from you 
  * Who the information will be shared with (if anyone) 
  * An opt out policy ? Access to your information (including how to update or correct inaccuracies) 
  * Safeguards in place to protect your information 
  * Other information about your privacy 

What personal information is being gathered by HotelThailand.com and how is this information being used?   
**Member Registration**  
When you become a HotelThailand.com member you provide your email address, a unique login name, password, and password validation. 

You can provide optional additional information during registration. The information will help us assist you better for several reasons including: (i) personal identification; (ii) to complete package reservation; (iii) to allow us to contact you for customer service, if necessary; (iv) to customize the content of our site to meet your specific needs; and (v) to make product improvements to HotelThailand.com. In addition, your email address is collected to send you an email message confirming your new member registration and each reservation you transact online. As a member you will occasionally receive updates from us about new product lines, special offers, and new HotelThailand.com services. However, you may always decline to receive these email messages. Please see our Opt Out  policy described below.   
  
**Member Profile**  
Members can choose to provide HotelThailand.com with travel preferences, credit card billing information, delivery address, and other personal information. This information is primarily used to assist members in making reservations quickly without having to type in the same information repeatedly. For example, members can add their favorite packages to their personal folder so that when a reservation is ready to be made, they can just fill the dates and number of persons travelling to make preliminary reservation. Moreover, our travel coordinators can recommend packages to best fit your preferences, arrange travel details according to your needs, and send information on topics that you're interested in.   
**Online Votes**  
HotelThailand.com values opinions and comments from members, and hosts a section for online votes. This service is entirely optional for all members. Typically, the information is aggregated and used to make improvements to HotelThailand.com and to develop appealing content, features, and promotions for members. All votes are anonymous.   
**Cookies**  
"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. HotelThailand.com uses cookies in several ways. We use cookies to allow you to login without having to type your login name each time. Instead, only your password is needed to access the system. We also use cookies to track usage of the "Guest" path and to serve advertisements through our advertising networks. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but if you prefer, you can edit your browser options to block them in the future.   
**IP Addresses**  
HotelThailand.com collects IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our servers and for system administration.

Please be aware that we have links on our site which may collect personally identifiable information about you. This Privacy Statement does not cover the information practices or policies of such Web sites.   
  
**Who will the information be shared with, if anyone?**  
When you reserve or purchase travel services through HotelThailand.com, we provide information about you to the airline, car rental agency, hotel, travel agency or other involved third party to ensure the successful fulfillment of your travel arrangements. We do not sell individual customer names or other private profile information to third parties and have no intention of doing so in the future. Occasionally, HotelThailand.com will hire a third party to act on our behalf for projects such as market research surveys and will provide information to these third parties specifically for use in connection with these projects. The information we provide to such third parties is protected by a confidentiality agreement and is to be used solely for completing the specific project.   
** Opt Out Policy**  
At anytime, you can unsubscribe to any features provided by HotelThailand.com or request that HotelThailand.com does not collect any personal information that is not essential to your booking. 

As a member you will occasionally receive email updates from us about new product lines, special offers, and new HotelThailand.com services. We hope you will find these updates interesting. Of course, if you would rather not receive them, please click on the unsubscribe link in the e-mail message. HotelThailand.com reserves the right to limit membership to those who will accept emails as it is the most effective method for our travel coordinators to reach you.   
  
**How can you access, update or correct your information?**  
At any time , you can view and / or update your personal profile , which includes member registration and travel preferences information , by following the your account link on our web page at [www.hotelthailand.com ](http://www.hotelthailand.com/)

What safeguards are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of your information? All information you provide to HotelThailand.com is transmitted using SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption. SSL is a proven coding system that lets your browser automatically encrypt, or scramble, data before you send it to us.   
  
**What other information should I know about my privacy?**  
HotelThailand.com contains links to other Web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are entering another Web site for which HotelThailand.com has no responsibility. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of all such sites as their policies may be materially different from HotelThailand.com's Privacy Statement. Of course, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and any account information. Please be very careful, responsible, and alert with this information, especially whenever you're online. 

In addition to the circumstances described above, HotelThailand.com may disclose member information if required to do so by law, court order, as requested by other government or law enforcement authority, or in the good faith belief that disclosure is otherwise necessary or advisable including, without limitation, to protect the rights or properties of HotelThailand.com or when we have reason to believe that disclosing the information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be causing interference with our rights or properties, whether intentionally or otherwise, or when anyone else could be harmed by such activities. 

Any material changes in the way HotelThailand.com uses personal information will be described in future versions of this Privacy Statement. Of course, you may always submit concerns regarding our Privacy Statement or our privacy practices to services(a)HotelThailand.com [(a) = @] . Please reference the privacy policy in your subject line. HotelThailand.com will attempt to respond to all reasonable concerns or inquiries.
